Ohh. She's cute.Her eyes are cute.
哇哦   妹子长得好可爱  圆圆的眼睛超可爱
She's movin fast. She's faster faster fast... You got it.
跟着节奏做鬼脸  好快好快好快   哦  学会了
Ah. You got it too! I can't I do what you do but I'm gonna try.
啊  诶   你也学会了  我不会但我还是要玩起来
You looking fly you looking fly.
你好帅   你好帅
How's he moving his eyes like this?
这眼睛怎么动的啊
Wow, how did he swtich his face...
我的老天鹅诶   这脸
His lip!
看他的嘴唇
His lips are flexible.
这小伙嘴皮子挺溜啊
That's cheating. That's cheating. Anyone can do that.
不带你们这么玩的  只要找个女朋友
That is cool tho. The tape!
这个胶带让这小两口玩活了都
And I like his outfit.
我喜欢这小伙的衣服
You guys.Hey! Hey! Hey!
兄弟们一起  嘿   嘿   嘿
Ouch!
(好疼)
Are those bunny ears?
这是兔子耳朵吗
Cute little girl and just like...
这小姐姐真是萌坏我了
How these ears moving?
这可爱的耳朵怎么动的
That is not even on her face.
耳朵就像长在了她的头上